[
    {
      "id": 13,
      "category": "Types of Computers",
      "question": "Which of the following is the most powerful type of computer?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Super micro" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Super conductor" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Microcomputer" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Super computer" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "Mega frame" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Super computer" }
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "category": "Technical Knowledge",
      "question": "Which of the following people probably has the least amount of technical knowledge?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Programmer" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "User" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "System analyst" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Computer operator" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "Computer professional" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "User" }
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "category": "Central Processing Unit",
      "question": "The Central Processing Unit (CPU) consists of:",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Input, output and processing" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Control unit, primary storage & secondary storage" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Control unit, arithmetic-logic unit, primary storage" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "None of the above" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "All of the above" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Control unit, arithmetic-logic unit, primary storage" }
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "category": "Computer Components",
      "question": "This is the part of the computer system that one can touch",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "hardware" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "data" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "software" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "input" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "hardware" }
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "category": "Optical Storage",
      "question": "Reusable optical storage will typically have the acronym ___",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "CD" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "RW" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "DVD" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "ROM" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "RW" }
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "category": "Computer Software",
      "question": "The __________ tells the computer how to use its components.",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "utility" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "network" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "operating system" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "application program" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "operating system" }
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "category": "Utility Programs",
      "question": "A(n) __________ is a program that makes the computer easier to use.",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "application" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "utility" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "network" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "operating system" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "utility" }
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "category": "Computer History",
      "question": "The ‘Difference Analyzer’ was created in the early 1920s by __",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Peter Norton" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Douglas Knuth" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Vannevar Bush" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Alan Kay" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Vannevar Bush" }
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "category": "Networks",
      "question": "The most important or powerful computer in a typical network.",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "desktop" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "network client" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "network server" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "network station" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "network server" }
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "category": "Accessing Supercomputers",
      "question": "To access a mainframe or supercomputer, users often use a ___",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "terminal" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "node" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "desktop" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "handheld" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "terminal" }
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "category": "Database Design",
      "question": "What database function allows you to define the data your database is storing?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Definition wizard" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Query Function" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Design view" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Data dictionary" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Data dictionary" }
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "category": "Database Attributes",
      "question": "If you wanted to tell the database management system that a specific attribute contained numbers only, what would you need to set?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Data category" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Data type" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Data dictionary" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Data definition" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Data type" }
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "category": "Database Keys",
      "question": "What key distinctly identifies a record in a database table?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Main key" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Primary key" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Principal key" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Major key" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Primary key" }
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "category": "Database Keys",
      "question": "What key links records from one database table to a record or records in another database table?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Primary key" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Principal key" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Foreign key" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Link key" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Foreign key" }
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "category": "Database Relationships",
      "question": "When you link one database table to another database table, what are you creating?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Primary link" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Connectivity" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Relationships" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Referential integrity" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Relationships" }
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "category": "Database Management",
      "question": "What would you need to establish if you wanted to insure that the key in one database table was the same as a key in another database table?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Top-level grouping" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Connectivity" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Referential integrity" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Field properties" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Referential integrity" }
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "category": "Database Tools",
      "question": "What database tool would you use to find answers to your questions about data stored in your database?",
      "options": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Queries" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Tables" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Show" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Q&A" },
        { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
      ],
      "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Queries" }
    },
    {
          "id": 30,
          "category": "Excel Worksheets",
          "question": "When we describe, or define, the categories of information we collect in an Excel worksheet, what type of table are we creating?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Categorization" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Classification" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Explanation" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "List definition" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "List definition" }
        },
        {
          "id": 31,
          "category": "Excel Functions",
          "question": "If you wished to limit what you would see on an Excel worksheet, what data function would you use?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Sort" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Filter" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Conditional format" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Data analysis" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Filter" }
        },
        {
          "id": 32,
          "category": "Excel Tools",
          "question": "If you wished to highlight, not hide, some information in a worksheet because it met some criteria, what Excel tool would you use?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Table" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Format" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Conditional Format" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Filter" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Conditional Format" }
        },
        {
          "id": 33,
          "category": "Excel Features",
          "question": "What Excel tool allows you to create quickly and automatically summary data from a large data set?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Conditional formatting" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Sorting" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Pivot tables" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Field lists" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Pivot tables" }
        },
        {
          "id": 34,
          "category": "Excel Filtering",
          "question": "When creating a custom filter in Excel, which of the following would not be considered a Boolean operator?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "If" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "And" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Or" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Not" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "If" }
        },
        {
          "id": 35,
          "category": "Excel Worksheet Habits",
          "question": "Which of the following is a good habit to get into when creating a worksheet?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Placing titles for columns in the first row of data" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Using conditional formatting to spot spelling errors" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Inserting comments in each cell to define that data or type of data" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Grouping records according to some classification" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Placing titles for columns in the first row of data" }
        },
        {
          "id": 36,
          "category": "Information Collections",
          "question": "What term is used to describe a collection of information that you can use to build reports or discover facts about an environment?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Database" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Web site" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Wiki" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Relation" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Database" }
        },
        {
          "id": 37,
          "category": "Database Software",
          "question": "Microsoft's Access and Corel's Paradox are both examples of which type of software?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Network database systems" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Relational database systems" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Flat-file database systems" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Hierarchical database systems" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Relational database systems" }
        },
        {
          "id": 38,
          "category": "Database Models",
          "question": "What type of graphical model is used to define a database?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Flowchart" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "E-R diagram" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Organizational model" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Programming model" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "E-R diagram" }
        },
        {
          "id": 39,
          "category": "Database Development",
          "question": "After you develop a model for your database, you should then _____ it before building it.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "normalize" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "design" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "plan" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "approve" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "normalize" }
        },
        {
          "id": 40,
          "category": "Database Structure",
          "question": "Which of the following contains information about the structure of a database?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Database management system" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Data dictionary" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Data repository" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Data warehouse" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Data dictionary" }
        },
        {
          "id": 41,
          "category": "Programming Language Rules",
          "question": "The rules of a language are called its __________.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "structure" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "code" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "syntax" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "rigidity" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "syntax" }
        },
        {
          "id": 42,
          "category": "Programming Language Portability",
          "question": "A language that can be written on one platform and executed on another platform is said to be __________.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "portable" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "robust" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "third generation" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "dynamic" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "portable" }
        },
        {
          "id": 43,
          "category": "Programming Technology",
          "question": "__________ is Microsoft’s latest entry into the programming arena.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Java" },
            { "id": 2, "text": ".NET" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Visual Basic" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Pascal" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 2, "text": ".NET" }
        },
        {
          "id": 44,
          "category": "Web Content Development",
          "question": "A next-generation Web content development language, __________ typically refers to a suite of technologies that allow developers to store data in a readable format.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "HTML" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "XSL" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "XML" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "PHP" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "XML" }
        },
        {
          "id": 45,
          "category": "JavaScript Development",
          "question": "JavaScript was developed by __________ to run inside of web pages.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "Microsoft" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "Sun" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "Oracle" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Netscape" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Netscape" }
        },
        {
          "id": 46,
          "category": "XML Technology",
          "question": "This technology is used to convert XML into HTML.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "CSS" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "XHTML" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "PHP" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "XSL" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "XSL" }
        },
        {
          "id": 47,
          "category": "Windows Registry",
          "question": "The __________ is a special database that holds information about the computer’s user, installed programs and hardware devices.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "dynamic link library" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "initialization file" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "compiled help module" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "Windows Registry" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Windows Registry" }
        },
        {
          "id": 48,
          "category": "Programming Tools",
          "question": "A(n) __________ converts all the source code into machine code, creating an executable file.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "linker" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "compiler" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "assembler" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "interpreter" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "compiler" }
        },
        {
          "id": 49,
          "category": "Algorithm Definition",
          "question": "A series of steps that always results in an answer is the definition of __________.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "heuristic" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "flowchart" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "algorithm" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "pseudo code" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "algorithm" }
        },
        {
          "id": 50,
          "category": "Attribute Example",
          "question": "The color of an object is an example of a(n) __________.",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "text": "attribute" },
            { "id": 2, "text": "detail" },
            { "id": 3, "text": "listing" },
            { "id": 4, "text": "specification" },
            { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
          ],
          "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "attribute" }
        },
        {
              "id": 51,
              "category": "File Formats",
              "question": "A(n) __________ file contains information in an indexed and cross-linked format.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "executable" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "initialization" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "help" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "library" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "help" }
            },
            {
              "id": 52,
              "category": "Programming Concepts",
              "question": "A(n) __________ encapsulates data and functionality.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "structured program" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "selection statement" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "object" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "program" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "selection statement" }
            },
            {
              "id": 53,
              "category": "File Types",
              "question": "__________ are text files containing OS commands.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Initialization files" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Batch files" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Executable files" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Help files" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Batch files" }
            },
            {
              "id": 54,
              "category": "Internet Laws",
              "question": "The __________ prevents unlawful access to voice communications by wire.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Electronic Communications Privacy Act" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Freedom of Information Act" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "USA Patriot Act" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Privacy Act of 1974" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Electronic Communications Privacy Act" }
            },
            {
              "id": 55,
              "category": "Email Protection",
              "question": "Which of the following will not protect you from spam?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "spam blockers" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "e-mail rules" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "popup blocker" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "filters" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "popup blocker" }
            },
            {
              "id": 56,
              "category": "Internet Security",
              "question": "A __________’s main purpose is to prohibit unauthorized access to your computer via the Internet.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "popup blocker" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "firewall" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "spyware blocker" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "spam assassin" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "firewall" }
            },
            {
              "id": 57,
              "category": "Windows System Tools",
              "question": "To read the system messages and warnings, access the __________ in Windows.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "system manager" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "control panel" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "event viewer" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "message screen" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "event viewer" }
            },
            {
              "id": 58,
              "category": "Backup Procedures",
              "question": "To create a copy of files in the event of system failure, you create a __________.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "restore file" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "backup" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "firewall" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "redundancy" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "backup" }
            },
            {
              "id": 59,
              "category": "System Security",
              "question": "If configured correctly, the __________ will prevent interaction with your computer after a specified time period.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "firewall" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "filter" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "screen saver" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "popup blocker" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "virus" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "screen saver" }
            },
            {
              "id": 60,
              "category": "Data Recovery",
              "question": "To recover files from a backup, you perform a __________.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "restore" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "scan" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "unerase" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "copy" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "restore" }
            },
            {
              "id": 61,
              "category": "Security Threats",
              "question": "A __________ is anything that can cause harm.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "vulnerability" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "phish" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Threat" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "spoof" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of the above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Threat" }
            },
            {
              "id": 62,
              "category": "Security Threats",
              "question": "In the right setting a thief will steal your information by simply watching what you type.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "snagging" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "spying" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "social engineering" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "shoulder surfing" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "shoulder surfing" }
            },
            {
              "id": 63,
              "category": "Security Threats",
              "question": "---------- A hacker contacts you by phone or email and attempts to acquire your password.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "spoofing" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "phishing" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "spamming" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "bugging" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "phishing" }
            },
            {
              "id": 64,
              "category": "Power Protection",
              "question": "This power protection device includes a battery that provides a few minutes of power.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "surge suppressor" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "line conditioner" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "generator" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "UPS" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "UPS" }
            },
            {
              "id": 65,
              "category": "Security Threats",
              "question": "A hacker that changes or forges information in an electronic resource is engaging in __________.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "denial of service" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "sniffing" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "terrorism" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "data diddling" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "data diddling" }
            },
            {
              "id": 66,
              "category": "Security Threats",
              "question": "The __________ of a threat measures its potential impact on a system.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "vulnerabilities" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "countermeasures" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "degree of harm" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "susceptibility" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "none of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "degree of harm" }
            },
            {
              "id": 67,
              "category": "Web Concepts",
              "question": "Which of the following identifies a specific web page and its computer on the Web?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Web site" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Web site address" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "URL" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Domain Name" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Domain Name" }
            },
            {
              "id": 68,
              "category": "Software",
              "question": "Software, such as Explorer and Firefox, are referred to as _____.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Systems software" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Browsers" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Internet tools" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "None of these" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Browsers" }
            },
            {
              "id": 69,
              "category": "Internet Service Providers",
              "question": "Which following ISP is free?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "CompuServe" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "AOL" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "NetZero" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "MSN" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "NetZero" }
            },
            {
              "id": 70,
              "category": "Internet Infrastructure",
              "question": "When internet data leaves your campus, it normally goes to a(n) ______ before moving toward its destination.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Internet backbone" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Network access point" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Base station" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Communication system" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Network access point" }
            },
            {
              "id": 71,
              "category": "Internet Service Providers",
              "question": "MCI and AT&T are examples of which of the following?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Social networks" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Communications systems" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Internet service providers" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Mobisodes" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Internet service providers" }
            },
            {
              "id": 72,
              "category": "Telecommunications",
              "question": "What type of telecommunications hardware allows you to access the web?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Browser" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Modem" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "FTP protocol" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "IRC" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Modem" }
            },
            {
              "id": 73,
              "category": "Email",
              "question": "E-mail addresses separate the user name from the ISP using the __________ symbol",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "&" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "@" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "%" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "*" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "@" }
            },
            {
              "id": 74,
              "category": "Email Protocols",
              "question": "The mail server as defined in the text uses the __________ protocol",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "HTTP" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "FTP" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "POP" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "SMTP" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "POP" }
            },
            {
              "id": 75,
              "category": "Email",
              "question": "When sending an e-mail, the __________ line describes the contents of the message.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "to" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "subject" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "contents" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "CC" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "subject" }
            },
            {
              "id": 76,
              "category": "Email",
              "question": "Unsolicited commercial email is commonly known as __________.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "junk" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "hoaxes" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "spam" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "hypertext" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "spam" }
            },
            {
              "id": 77,
              "category": "Internet Protocols",
              "question": "News servers utilize __________ to distribute documents to readers.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "NNTP" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "NEWS" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "HTTP" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "FTP" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "NNTP" }
            },
            {
              "id": 78,
              "category": "Internet Forums",
              "question": "Discussion groups may have a __________ who monitors the postings and enforces the site’s rules.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "judge" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "sysop" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "narrator" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "censor" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "sysop" }
            },
            {
              "id": 79,
              "category": "Internet Forums",
              "question": "A message with replies on a newsgroup is often called a __________.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "post" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "list" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "thread" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "comment" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "thread" }
            },
            {
              "id": 80,
              "category": "Internet History",
              "question": "The Internet was originally a project for this government agency.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "ARPA" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "NSA" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "NSF" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "FCC" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "ARPA" }
            },
            {
              "id": 81,
              "category": "Web Concepts",
              "question": "A word in a web page that, when clicked, opens another document.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "anchor" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "URL" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Hyperlink" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "reference" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Hyperlink" }
            },
            {
              "id": 82,
              "category": "Networks",
              "question": "A network’s __________ is the central structure that connects other portions of the network.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "trunk" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "backbone" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "protocol" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "server" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "backbone" }
            },
            {
              "id": 83,
              "category": "Web Protocols",
              "question": "__________ is the protocol that supports linking from one web page to another page.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "HTML" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "IP" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "HTTP" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "FTP" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "HTTP" }
            },
            {
              "id": 84,
              "category": "Bookmarks",
              "question": "You can organize your bookmarks using __________.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "structures" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "containers" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "folders" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "menus" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "folders" }
            },
            {
              "id": 85,
              "category": "Browsing",
              "question": "The browser’s __________ keeps a list of web pages you have visited during the current session.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "history" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "cache" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "favorites" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "trail" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of the above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "history" }
            },
            {
              "id": 86,
              "category": "Search Engines",
              "question": "A __________ organizes the web into categories.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "search engine" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "encyclopedia" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "archive" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "directory" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "directory" }
            },
            {
              "id": 87,
              "category": "Search Techniques",
              "question": "To match all of the words in your search, the Boolean __________ operator should be used.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "and" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "or" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "xor" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "both" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "and" }
            },
            {
              "id": 88,
              "category": "Accounting and IT",
              "question": "What type of accountants may recommend controls for an organization's computer systems?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Environment accountant" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Internal accountant" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Government accountant" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Public accountant" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Internal accountant" }
            },
            {
              "id": 89,
              "category": "Accounting and IT",
              "question": "Which IT area is well-established in Accounting?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Multimedia systems" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Web development" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Statistical analysis" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Accounting Information Systems" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Accounting Information Systems" }
            },
            {
              "id": 90,
              "category": "Accounting and IT",
              "question": "How do accountants quickly research new government rules and regulations?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "With an internal database management systems" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Through the Web" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "With an external database management systems" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Through organizational network systems" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Through the Web" }
            },
            {
              "id": 91,
              "category": "Security Threats",
              "question": "Which computer virus records every movement you make on your computer?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Malware Android" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Key logger" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "DoS" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Trapper" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Key logger" }
            },
            {
              "id": 92,
              "category": "Security Threats",
              "question": "What program would you use to gain administrative rights to someone's computer?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Bot" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Executive Android" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Rootkit" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Trojan horse" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "none of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Rootkit" }
            },
            {
              "id": 93,
              "category": "Programming",
              "question": "A remote control that is used to turn on or off some machine is also called a(n) _____.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "class" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "interface" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "message" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "instance" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "interface" }
            },
            {
              "id": 94,
              "category": "Object-Oriented Programming",
              "question": "In a student grading system, Student Last Name, Student Address, and Final Course Grade would all be classified as what?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Inheritance" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Information" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Encapsulation" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Polymorphism" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "none of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Information" }
            },
            {
              "id": 95,
              "category": "Object-Oriented Programming",
              "question": "What part of object-oriented technology defines superclass and subclass relationships?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Inheritance" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Scalability" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Encapsulation" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Polymorphism" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Inheritance" }
            },
            {
              "id": 96,
              "category": "Object-Oriented Programming",
              "question": "When an object has many forms, it has _____.",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Inheritance" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Scalability" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Encapsulation" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Polymorphism" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Polymorphism" }
            },
            {
              "id": 97,
              "category": "Object-Oriented Programming",
              "question": "What programming language model is organized around \"objects\" rather than \"actions\"?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Java" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "OOB" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Perl" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "C++" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "OOB" }
            },
            {
              "id": 98,
              "category": "Programming",
              "question": "What are the instructions called that tell a system what, how, and when to do something?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Object-oriented technology approach" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Object-oriented database" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Program" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Database management" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Program" }
            },
            {
              "id": 99,
              "category": "Programming",
              "question": "What common technique attempts to save time and energy by reducing redundant work in object-oriented programming?",
              "options": [
                { "id": 1, "text": "Reduce lines of programming" },
                { "id": 2, "text": "Reuse of code" },
                { "id": 3, "text": "Reduce size of systems being developed" },
                { "id": 4, "text": "Merging different systems together" },
                { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
              ],
              "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Reuse of code" }
            },
            {
                  "id": 100,
                  "category": "Programming Languages",
                  "question": "What kind of programming language is Java?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Object-oriented programming language" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Relational programming language" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Sixth-generation programming language" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Database management programming language" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Object-oriented programming language" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 101,
                  "category": "Internet Technology",
                  "question": "What type of internet technology sends information to you without you requesting that information?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "F2b2C" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Infoware" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Push" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Wiki" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Push" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 102,
                  "category": "Web Development",
                  "question": "What is the second generation of the Web called?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "New web" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Emerging space" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Second life" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Web 2.0" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Web 2.0" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 103,
                  "category": "Web Technology",
                  "question": "What type of web technology allows its community members to continuously change the contents on a web site?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Intelligent bots" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Social networks" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Wiki" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Blog" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Wiki" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 104,
                  "category": "Web Technology",
                  "question": "What type of web technology provides news that can automatically download right to your desktop?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Social network" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "RSS feed" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Podcast" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Wiki" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "RSS feed" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 105,
                  "category": "Web Technology",
                  "question": "What type of web technology creates an online community where people can make statements and others can read and respond to those statements?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "I-Journal" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Podcast" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "ASP" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Blog" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Blog" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 106,
                  "category": "Web Technology",
                  "question": "What type of technology allows you to verbally speak with someone over the Internet?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Wiki" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Social network" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Ephone" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "VoIP" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "VoIP" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 107,
                  "category": "Social Media",
                  "question": "What kind of environment is Facebook or MySpace part of?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Wiki" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Blog" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Social networking" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "VoIP" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Social networking" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 108,
                  "category": "Technology and Society",
                  "question": "What term refers to living life through technology?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Virtual living" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "E-living" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Virtual space" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "E-Society" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "E-Society" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 109,
                  "category": "Virtual Reality",
                  "question": "What 3-D environment allows you to speak to someone who is far away but, at the same time, see them as a holographic image?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "CAVE" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Virtual space" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "E-space" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "VoIP" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "CAVE" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 110,
                  "category": "Information Security",
                  "question": "What type of technology allows you to use your finger, eye, or voice print to secure your information resources?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Haptics" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Caves" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Biometrics" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "RFID" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All of above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Biometrics" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 111,
                  "category": "Ethics in Technology",
                  "question": "In reference to your ethical structure, how much do you identify with the person or persons who will receive the benefit or suffer the harm is called which of the following?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Consequences" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Relatedness" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Likelihood of effect" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Society's opinion" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "none of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Relatedness" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 112,
                  "category": "Information Security",
                  "question": "Which tracking program records every keystroke you make on the computer?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "ITrack/ULead" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "eFollow" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Key logger" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Stalking software" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "none of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Key logger" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 113,
                  "category": "Identity Theft",
                  "question": "What is a common medium used for thieves to steal others' identities?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Telephone" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Pick pocketing" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Burglary" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Email" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "none of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Email" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 114,
                  "category": "Cybersecurity",
                  "question": "What is it called when you are rerouted from your requested internet site to another, undesired site?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Phishing" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Pharming" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Redirecting" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Hijacking" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Pharming" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 115,
                  "category": "Cybersecurity",
                  "question": "What is the term that refers to an ad hidden inside software that you downloaded from an internet site?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Spam" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Phish" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Cookie" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Adware" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Adware" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 116,
                  "category": "Internet Security",
                  "question": "What type of monitoring file is commonly used on and accepted from Internet sites?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Phishes" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Smartware" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Cookies" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Trojans" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Cookies" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 117,
                  "category": "Ethics in Technology",
                  "question": "Ideally, your sense of what is ethical should tell you which of the following?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "What to do" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Who to do it to" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "When to do it" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Where to do it" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "What to do" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 118,
                  "category": "Cybersecurity",
                  "question": "What type of software secretly collects information about you and your internet habits?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Detectware" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Spam" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Spyware" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Pharming" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All the above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Spyware" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 119,
                  "category": "Intellectual Property",
                  "question": "In an educational setting, instructors have access to and use a whole host of copyrighted materials. What allows these individuals to make use of these materials?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Patent laws" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Fair Use Doctrine" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Intellectual property laws" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Higher educational board" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All the above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Fair Use Doctrine" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 120,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "What type of information systems environment reuses self-contained blocks of code in its systems?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Modular systems" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Block based coding" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Component programming" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Service-oriented architecture" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Service-oriented architecture" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 121,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "What term refers to the structure, and substructures, of an organization's information systems?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Subsystems" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "System formations" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "IT Configurations" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Infrastructure" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Infrastructure" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 122,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "When two or more computers are able to share information, what is this called?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Shared systems" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Interoperability" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Information interchange" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Data exchange" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All the above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "Interoperability" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 123,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "When there is little or no exchange of information within an organization's information systems, we say that the systems are _____.",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Independent" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Autonomous" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Decentralized" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Self-sufficient" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Decentralized" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 124,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "When information and processing are spread throughout the organization via a network, we say the systems are _____.",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Dependent" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Reliant" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Distributed" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Self-supporting" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All the above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 3, "text": "Distributed" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 125,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "When one computer provides services to another computer, the environment is a(n) _____ infrastructure.",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Client/server" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Dependent" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Reliant" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Independent" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Client/server" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 126,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "What type of infrastructure are most enterprise applications employing?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Network" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Distributed" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Complex" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Tiered" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Tiered" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 127,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "When you continuously measure yourself against your peers, you are employing _____.",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Benchmarking" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "Balancing" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Stability" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "Reliability" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 1, "text": "Benchmarking" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 128,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "What is the term used to describe the organization of a company's information systems department?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "IT structure" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "IS department" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Information systems design" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "IT configuration" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "All the above" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 2, "text": "IS department" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 129,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "Which of the following is a major component of an information system's infrastructure?",
                  "options": [
                    { "id": 1, "text": "Database systems" },
                    { "id": 2, "text": "End users" },
                    { "id": 3, "text": "Procedures" },
                    { "id": 4, "text": "All the above" },
                    { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "All the above" }
                },
                {
                  "id": 130,
                  "category": "Information Systems",
                  "question": "What type of infrastructure do companies employ to work with their customers?",
                  "options": [
                  { "id": 1, "text": "Network" },
                  { "id": 2, "text": "Distributed" },
                  { "id": 3, "text": "Client/server" },
                  { "id": 4, "text": "Customer-facing" },
                  { "id": 5, "text": "None of these" }
                  ],
                  "answer": { "id": 4, "text": "Customer-facing" }
                }

              ]
              
             
          
          
        
     
      
  
  